Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Hans Weissenstein Negatives PHOTOS 019 001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Dedicated Days/Weeks/Celebrations.
  - Afro-American Week Displays PS 25 [# 12392-4: Teacher Roberta Fass tells her students about labor leaders, A. Philip Randolph. Left to Right: Edgar Diaz, Darnell Norris, Neal McCord, Larry Gilliam, Roberta Fass, and Tyrone Temple.], Feb 13, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12392)
  - PS 129 Afro-American Week, Feb 20, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12402)
  - PS 129 Broglia West [Students reading Langston Hughes poetry, showing off African-American pictures, magazines and history posters.], Mar 12, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12440)
  - PS 307 Earth Day, Apr 22, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12528)
  - Afro-American Exhibit Display PS 151, Jun 3, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12636)
  - African Art Fordham [?], Jul 21, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12727)
  - PS 70 Puerto Rican Discovery Day, Nov 17, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12898)
  - Puerto Rican Discovery Day - Taft HS, Nov 18, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12904)
  - Puerto Rico Day - 6 Schools Bronx, Nov 19, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12909)
  - Bronx Schools Martin Luther King Day, Jan 11, 1971 (Box 17, Item 12999)
  - Howard Taft H.S. - Martin Luther King Exhibit & Performance, Jan 13, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13008)
  - PS 208 - Martin L. King Celebration, Jan 14, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13009)
  - IS 293 Brooklyn Nathan Hale Production [Appears to be a celebration of African heritage and culture - students participating in African dance and drumming.], Jan 14, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13014)
  - District 28 [Dr. Martin Luther] King Program, Jan 21, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13027)
  - Chinese New Year PS 130, Jan 26, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13032)
  - PS 23 Manhattan Chinese New Year Play, Jan 28, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13042)
  - John Brown HS Martin L. King Display, Jan 29, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13043)
  - PS 332 Brooklyn Black Music through the Years, Feb 8, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13062)
  - JHS 232 Brooklyn Black History Program, Feb 11, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13072)
  - PS 159 Brooklyn Black History Celebration, Feb 11, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13070)
  - PS 45 Queens - Negro History - Performance for parents, Feb 23, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13093)
  - PS 396-327 Brooklyn Fiesta Panamerica, Apr 6, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13195)
  - JHS 296 Brooklyn Pan American Show, Apr 23, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13219)
  - PS 130 Manhattan Chinese - Puerto Rican - Day, Apr 30, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13253)
  - PS 150 Bronx Crop Principal Black & Puerto Rican Culture, May 5, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13264)
  - District 28 Queens overcrowded classes demonstration, May 6, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13268)
  - PS 128 M King Film Premiere - Para-Professional - PS 128 M, May 22, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13332)
  - P[uerto] R[ican] Discovery Day Brooklyn PS 284 Brooklyn, Nov 18, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13635)
  - PS 60 Bronx P[uerto] R[ican] Program, Nov 18, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13638)
  - PS 297 Brooklyn Puerto Rico Discovery Day, Nov 22, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13660)
  - Thanksgiving Day Feast PS 188 Brooklyn, Marta Gross, Labell Harrison, Nov 24, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13666)
  - International food festival Wingate HS Brooklyn, Stanley Finger, Dec 3, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13686)
  - PS 299 Award Winners at Black Expo, Dec 8, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13709)
  - PS 127 Queens Martin Luther King Day, Jan 18, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13799)
  - Demonstration PS15, Jan 26, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13811)
  - Chinese New Year PS 23, Feb 10, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13829)
  - PS 244 K Brooklyn Americana USA, Feb 16, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13842)
  - Chinese New Year PS 2, Feb 17, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13851)
  - Afro American History PS 224 Brooklyn, Feb 17, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13852)
  - JHS 45 Manhattan Afro American History week, Feb 18, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13848)
  - PS 157, District 7, Brooklyn, Negro History Week, Feb 18, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13853)
  - PS 282 Negro History, Feb 25, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13863)
  - PS 75 Brooklyn Pan-American Day & Fashion Show, Apr 14, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13939)
  - PS 198 Manhattan Pan A[merican] Fiesta, Apr 21, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13951)
  - PS 9 Brooklyn Martin Luther King Statue, Apr 21, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13952)
  - IS 10 Manhattan, Bro[c?]k Peters Auditorium, F[rederick] Douglas Day, May 19, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14013)
  - Sommers [?] JHS 252 International Festival, Jun 6, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14054)
  - African Exhibit [and ribbon cutting], Oct 17, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14455)
- Series VIII: Demonstrations/Rallies.
  - 3 Films of Amateur St. Johns Picket line [UFCT], undated (Box 6, Item 10730)
  - Teachers' Guild [Demonstration calling for cost of living adjustment.], Mar 12, 1950 (Box 1, Item 94)
  - Teachers' Guild Picketing City Hall [Collection includes corresponding prints.], Apr 14, 1953 (Box 1, Item 1110)
  - Teachers' Guild - Pickets "Wake up Mr. & Mrs. NY", Jan 13, 1954 (Box 1, Item 1575)
  - Teachers' Guild [Two men holding sign that reads "Higher Salaries = More Teachers = Better Schools; Raise Teachers' Salaries; Work Through Your Parents Ass'n, Your Civic Club, Your Union".], Jan 7, 1958 (Box 1, Item 4603)
  - Teachers' Guild - Rally @ Washington Irving HS, Feb 5, 1959 (Box 2, Item 4672)
  - Teachers' Guild - snowy day pickets @ Board of Education, Dec 21, 1959 (Box 2, Item 5318)
  - St. Nicholas Arena - Teachers with Placards, Mar 25, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5529)
  - St. Nicholas Arena - wide shot, Mar 25, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5529)
  - Teachers St. Nicholas Arena, Mar 25, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5529)
  - United Federation of Teachers picket line Woolworths, 42nd st. [Civil Rights: UFT Supports Sit-Ins], Jun 25, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5779)
  - Pre- strike rally - Placard-holders, Oct 19, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5908)
  - Dave Selden addressing pre-strike rally, Oct 19, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5908)
  - Pre-strike rally [back of speakers' heads], Oct 19, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5908)
  - Picket line Board of Education, Jun 6, 1961 (Box 2, Item 6421)
  - Picket line, Jun 6, 1961 (Box 2, Item 6421)
  - Picket line (long view), Jun 6, 1961 (Box 2, Item 6421)
  - Rally Brooklyn, Feb 28, 1963 (Box 2, Item 7478)
  - Rally HS of Fashion, Mar 20, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7539)
  - Rockefeller Office [Man holding "Veto the Index" sign; appears to be a demonstration in front of NYS Governor Nelson Rockefeller's office (street number 22).], Mar 22, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 7542)
  - City Hall Rally, Apr 3, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7570)
  - Vigil, May 1, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7635)
  - City Hall Picket line, May 7, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8306)
  - Board of Education Pickets & Hotel St. George Rally, Jul 1, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8505)
  - Camp Teachers Rally Washington Irving HS, Jul 29, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8473)
  - College Teachers Picket line, Oct 23, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8620)
  - Picket Line Welfare Workers, Jan 12, 1965 (Box 4, Item 8747)
  - Welfare Workers Picket Line at City Hall, Jan 18, 1965 (Box 4, Item 8774)
  - [UFCT] Picket Line Board of Higher Education, Nov 19, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9417)
  - St. John's Rally Manhattan Center, Dec 29, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9499)
  - UFCT Picket Line St. Johns Brooklyn, Jan 4, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9502)
  - Board of Education Picket Line - Summer Teachers, Aug 26, 1966 (Box 5, Item 10034)
  - [March from] Seward High to City Hall, Feb 16, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10300)
  - PS 113 [Portables demonstration; "Get rid of the portables. They're little more than -HUTS-" and "We need a wing for Quality Education" signs on a coach bus with women and children standing in front.], Feb 17, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10304)
  - JHS 98 Demonstration Board of Education, Mar 14, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10356)
  - ["Assembly"] Demonstration Marc Ballroom, Mar 21, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10386)
  - Picket Line Bedford Stuyvesant, May 19, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10495)
  - Voc[ational] Teachers Picket Board of Education, Jun 9, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10559)
  - M.E.S. Picket Line City Hall, Jun 22, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10586)
  - PS 131 Picket, Jun 28, 1967 (Box 6, Item 10758)
  - Van Buren HS Jamaica [demonstration by Parent Teacher Coalition to restore funds cut from budget.], May 7, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11188)
  - PS 117 East 109 Street Picket, May 7, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11189)
  - District 19 Brooklyn [children and adults demonstrating for restoration of funds cut from budget], May 7, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11190)
  - Ocean Hill Demonstration City Hall [UFT Pres. Albert Shanker speaking from atop a truck to crowd with umbrellas at City Hall rally during Ocean Hill/Brownsville crisis.], May 24, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11238)
  - Demonstration Little City Hall Brooklyn, Jun 16, 1968 (Box 8, Item 11971)
  - Andrew Stein; Buses and Rally, Sep 16, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11359)
  - District Super[intendent?] Montgomery Str. Picket, Sep 25, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11372)
  - City Hall Rally, Oct 17, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11428)
  - Vigil Gracie Mansion, Oct 25, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11456)
  - Headshot + O'Neill Demonstration [signs read "Unionism Yes, Racism No" and "Self-Determination for Black Communities"] [Headshots of Unidentified Individual], Nov 4, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11473)
  - Madison Square Garden [Appears to be a meeting of all UFT chapters/members. Different chapters and school/district representatives are noticeable, holding up signs of their delegations.], Nov 17, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11502)
  - WBAI [A demonstration of the Jewish Defense League calling to keep Julius Lester off the air. Appears a counter-demonstration is taking place by a group called "Whites Against White Violence." Unidentified individuals being arrested by police.], Jan 29, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11628)
  - Board of Education PS 39 Pickets, Mar 24, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11737)
  - PS 39 Pachelo [includes teacher seated at her desk in empty classroom and shots of protest signs written on the blackboard, including "Parents demand the teachers get out" and "Mr. Acosto is not wanted."], Mar 25, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11742)
  - Board of Education [Protest] 2 Bridges Picket, Mar 26, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11747)
  - City Hall UFCT Pickets, Apr 18, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11786)
  - Picket line 182 Street PS 194, May 13, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11875)
  - Picket line Boro Hall 2 Bridges at Bank, May 16, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11887)
  - [Demonstration at] Board of Education, Jun 11, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11964)
  - Demonstration PS 67 Bronx, Jun 20, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11977)
  - PS 61 Manhattan Demonstration, Sep 8, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12034)
  - Picket line Distr. Board of Ed [at] 1967 Turnbull Avenue [Bronx], Oct 20, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12130)
  - Vito, Washington Irving H. S. & Vigil, 260 Park, Nov 12, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12197)
  - Picket line [for] Deaf [classrooms] at City Hall, Dec 11, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12273)
  - Demonstration in Brooklyn, Jan 5, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12312)
  - PS 6 Demonstration Abe Levine [Includes shots of damage to school and Levine being interviewed by WEVD Radio.], Mar 23, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12456)
  - Demonstration at Board of Education, Mar 24, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12460)
  - Demonstration Hunts Point, Mar 25, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12465)
  - PS 50 Queens Demonstration, Apr 9, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12498)
  - City Hall PS 50 Mini School Demonstration, Apr 13, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12507)
  - Demonstration Carlton Ave to Board of Education, May 21, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12606)
  - Jail - Demonstration, May 26, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12614)
  - PS 211 Brooklyn Demonstration, Jun 2, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12637)
  - PS 87 Manhattan Demonstration for more Teachers & Para-Pros., Jun 8, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12660)
  - Demonstration PS 198 [Third] Ave, Jun 9, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12659)
  - District PS 20 Demonstration, Jun 11, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12679)
  - Rally City Hall - United for Better Schools Shot w/ [Al] Shanker & [Dave] Selden standing on a raised platform, Jun 15, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12681)
  - Board of Education Brandeis HS Demonstration, Jun 17, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12693)
  - PS 247 Brooklyn Mini School Demonstration, Jun 17, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12690)
  - Board of Education Picket line, Sep 10, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12743)
  - Parent Boycott School PS 11 Bronx, Sep 14, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12746)
  - Albert Shanker at PS 11 Bronx Boycott, Sep 17, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12757)
  - Demonstration IS 44, Sep 21, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12765)
  - Demonstration PS 167 Brooklyn, Sep 28, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12780)
  - Demonstration: City Hall - Brooklyn Bridge - City Hall Board of Ed, Oct 6, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12799)
  - School for Deaf, 23rd St & 2, 3, Ave. Traffic Light Demonstration, Oct 7, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12800)
  - PS 48 Bronx Boycott School, Oct 14, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12812)
  - PS 186 Manhattan Demonstration & Meeting & Old Building, Dec 1, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12929)
  - Secretaries & Teachers Large Rally Board of Education, Dec 15, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12964)
  - PS 50 Queens stop light demonstration, Jan 14, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13010)
  - PS 147 Queens Boycott Overcrowding [?], Feb 8, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13056)
  - JHS 57 K Brooklyn Picket line, Feb 18, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13079)
  - PS 262 Brooklyn Demonstration, Feb 24, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13094)
  - District 6 PS 186 Boycott, Feb 24, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13096)
  - City Hall Demonstration, Apr 27, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13230)
  - City Hall Demonstration WEP [Welfare Education Plan], Apr 30, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13256)
  - JHS 142 Brooklyn Demonstration, May 6, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13265)
  - PS 196 Queens overcrowded classes - demonstration, May 6, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13267)
  - Rally Francis Lewis HS Queens, May 6, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13271)
  - District 20 Funeral Procession to City Hall [Protest signs read "Budget Cuts Kill Public Schools"], May 7, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13273)
  - PS 167 Brooklyn Blocking Eastern Parkway Service Rd., May 10, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13277)
  - PS 20 Brooklyn Crowded Classes & Motorcade Boro Hall, May 13, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13294)
  - La Salle Jr. HS [PS 11?] Demonstration [Students and adults with signs reading "PS11 needs its MES program!" and "Confucius says: One MES school is better than none".], Jun 22, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13430)
  - Demonstration Para-Professional John Hill, District 5 Manhattan, Sep 14, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13476)
  - District #5 Demonstration, Oct 14, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13529)
  - Board of Education Demonstration Brooklyn John Hill, Oct 15, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13534)
  - PS 85 Astoria Street Blocking, Oct 22, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13560)
  - Demo - Boycott on Portable Schools PS 191 K Brooklyn, Oct 27, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13569)
  - Board of Education Portable Demonstration PS 191, Oct 29, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13576)
  - Vocational School Demonstration at City Hall, Nov 18, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13641)
  - PS 47 Bronx Puerto Rican [Discovery Day and Vocational Schools Rally], Nov 19, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13648)
  - PS 274 Brooklyn Puerto Rico Day, Nov 19, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13652)
  - PS 114 Bronx Puerto Rican [Discovery Day and Vocational Schools Rally], Nov 19, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13648)
  - Catholic Demonstration - Marc Ballroom [Catholic teachers on strike in front of Archdiocese of NY; shot of female teacher showing paycheck for $18.71 to camera with "Make Catholic Teaching a Career" sign around her neck.], Dec 2, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13688)
  - District 14 Human Relations course (Brooklyn), Jan 5, 1972 (Box 25, Item 13777)
  - PS 70 Queens Boycott, Feb 4, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13823)
  - Picket line Gov. Office, Handicapped, Mar 15, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13897)
  - PS 171 Manhattan Boycott, Apr 18, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13946)
  - College Teachers - Picket line Board of H. Education [Professional Staff Congress], Sep 13, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14085)
  - Prof. Staff Congress, Picket line, Brooklyn Comm. College, Feb 22, 1973 (Box 29, Item 14243)
  - Prof. Staff Congress, Lehman College, City College, Picket lines, Mar 27, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14288)
  - Prof. Staff Congress, Kingsboro Comm. College picketing, Apr 3, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14292)
- Series IX: UFT Elections and Voting.
  - NY Teachers Elections Hotel Astor, Mar 16, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5513)
  - Ballots Evans Hughes HS, Jun 29, 1961 (Box 2, Item 6460)
  - Ballot Counting, Apr 19, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7647)
  - Child Guidance Election, Apr 26, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7623)
  - Ballot Counting at New Yorker [Hotel], Jun 7, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7740)
  - Balloting Seward HS, Dec 4, 1963 (Box 3, Item 8010)
  - Ballots, May 11, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8311)
  - Ballot Counting, Jun 20, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10579)
  - Ballot Counting, Jun 12, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11277)
  - Balloting at Maritime Union, Sep 10, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11344)
  - Voting Maritime Union, Nov 17, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11503)
  - PS 205 Brooklyn letter Elections, Jan 8, 1969 (Box 6, Item 11585)
  - Julia Richman HS Elections, Jan 9, 1969 (Box 6, Item 11586)
  - Election District 11 Mario Raimo, Jan 16, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11600)
  - District 12 No Quorum, Jan 17, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11603)
  - Eastirwin [?] Drive 116 Street, Benj. Franklin HS, No Quorum, Jan 21, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11613)
  - Bayside HS, no quorum 26, Jan 23, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11614)
  - Marc Ballroom Election Meeting, May 22, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11905)
  - Ballots, Jun 5, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11940)
  - Para-Professionals Election Brandeis, Jun 25, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11984)
  - 2 Bridges gov. [?] Board Election, Sep 18, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12055)
  - District 25 Rep. Election JHS 169 Queens, Sep 26, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12068)
  - Para-Professional Vote, Apr 22, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12525)
  - Ballot Counting New Yorker, May 8, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12570)
  - Candidates [speaking to audience], Jun 1, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12632)
  - Elections [voters in booths], Jun 3, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12635)
  - Ballot Counting, Jun 3, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12643)
  - Ballot Counting, Jun 17, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12691)
  - Para-Professional heads & election Waldorf, Jun 22, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12701)
  - Para-Professionals Irving Plaza Voting, Aug 3, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12733)
  - [George] Altomare, Election Committee Swearing in, Apr 29, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13252)
  - Vote Counting, Jun 2, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13367)
  - Catholic Teachers Vote, Dec 13, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13726)
  - Local School Board Candidates, Mar 22, 1973 (Box 29, Item 14271)
  - District 5 Candidates, Congressman Rangel, Apr 7, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14296)
  - District 4 Candidates, Apr 7, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14297)
- Series X: Individuals
  - Congresswoman Bella Abzug (252 7th Ave), Oct 29, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13579)
  - [Sandra E.] Adickes [Collection includes a corresponding print.], Mar 7, 1967 (Box 6, Item 10736)
  - Mr. Adolph Portrait, Nov 10, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12186)
  - Forest Hill HS Queens Meeting of Students with Joan Agin about becoming teachers, Nov 23, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13661)
  - PS 86 Queens Joan Agin, Nov 4, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13600)
  - Alfredo, Matthew [headshots], Nov 2, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12867)
  - George Altomare speaking to crowd 260 P.A.S., Oct 28, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13572)
  - August Martin HS George Altomare, Oct 7, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13510)
  - [George] Altomare, Election Committee Swearing in, Apr 29, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13252)
  - Franklin K Lane HS, UFT Awards, George Altomare, Jun 29, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14075)
  - George Altomare addressing strike captains, Mar 23, 1962 (Box 3, Item 7545)
  - Board of Education [Robert] Atkin[s] Swearing-in, Apr 25, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8339)
  - Atkin[s], Robert [Collection includes two corresponding prints.], Apr 14, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8380)
  - [Robert] Atkin[s] & committee, Apr 24, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8279)
  - Robert] Atkin[s] Lecture PS 41, Apr 28, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8281)
  - PS 274 Congressman Badillo (Brooklyn), Jan 7, 1972 (Box 25, Item 13780)
  - Accounting Division [of the Anti-Defamation League Appeal] Waldorf Astoria [presenting awards to William Bateman and Stephen Chan], Mar 24, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13171)
  - Jerry Becker Portraits [Collection includes a corresponding print.], Apr 13, 1966 (Box 5, Item 9870)
  - Irving Berger Receives Back Pay, Jul 8, 1966 (Box 5, Item 10015)
  - Maurice Berube, Nov 21, 1966 (Box 6, Item 10735)
  - Susan Best Para-Professional, Portrait, undated (Box 30, Item 15611)
  - Ted Britton Dinner - Hilton Dinner, May 1, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13257)
  - Sandy Blair PS 95 Bronx End of Year Conference, Apr 26, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13342)
  - District 10 Sanford Blair, Feb 17, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11664)
  - District 10 Sanford Blair (Herbert Renner), Jan 20, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11608)
  - Bleecker, Ted [headshots], Apr 27, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12618)
  - Bleecker, Ted Repro[duction], Dec 20, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9519)
  - NY Teachers' Guild Mr. [Jeremiah] Bloom [headshots], Feb 12, 1953 (Box 1, Item 941)
  - Blum, Eugene Portrait, Feb 10, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9660)
  - Legisl. Comm. with Comptroller Boraccio, Jan 21, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9563)
  - PS 2 Visit by [Ted] Britton Britain's AAlbert Shanker, Apr 29, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13255)
  - Senator Brousfair, Dec 6, 1963 (Box 3, Item 8021)
  - Frank Brown headshot, Oct 27, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12846)
  - New Rep. Raymond Butler, Feb 25, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12408)
  - Candello Party, Jun 11, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12674)
  - Congressman [Hugh] Carey, Oct 29, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13585)
  - Congressman Celler, Oct 8, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13515)
  - Grape picket line [Support demonstration for United Farm Workers' grape boycott; one frame includes both UFW president Cesar Chavez apparently speaking with reporters and UFT president Albert Shanker speaking into microphone.], Oct 10, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12097)
  - HS of Fashion & Industries, Shirley Chisholm, Dec 17, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13741)
  - ATMC) [?] Albany [UFT members meeting with Assemblyman George A. Cincotta, Assemblyman Moses Weinstein and others], Mar 24, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11736)
  - Cornell Course [Charles] Cogen, Feb 20, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11674)
  - [Charles] Cogen, [Alice] Marsh, [Rebecca] Simonson (staff / officers), Oct 2, 1957 (Box 1, Item 3782)
  - [Charles] Cogen Teachers' Guild [headshots], Dec 5, 1952 (Box 1, Item 812)
  - Check pres[entation] Cogen, Selden, Aeberman [?], Jan 7, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8059)
  - Teachers' Guild Cara Cook [headshots] [Collection includes corresponding prints.], Mar 14, 1954 (Box 1, Item 1734)
  - Deputy Mayor [Timothy] Costello, Feb 10, 1966 (Box 4, Item 9658)
  - Teachers' Guild Norman Cousins Waldorf luncheon, Mar 2, 1958 (Box 1, Item 4038)
  - District 6 Bruce Davidson, Feb 7, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11648)
  - PS 305 Brooklyn Ossie Davis & Classes, Jan 21, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13805)
  - PAC DeFalco [seated with others], Feb 18, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13846)
  - Vito DeLeonardis Portrait, Nov 9, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9517)
  - Headshots [Mario DeSiepano, Rob Millen, Ann Kessler], Jul 21, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12726)
  - Para-Prof. At PS 47 [Mrs. Jeanette] DiLorenzo, Mar 10, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12430)
  - District 15, John Jay HS, Jeanette DiLorenzo, Jan 20, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11605)
  - Teachers' Guild Rebecca Dimonson Repro[duction], Sep 22, 1953 (Box 1, Item 1297)
  - PS JHS 10 District 23 Vinicio Donato, Feb 24, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11681)
  - Contract Signing Board of Education James Donavon, Feb 10, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8127)
  - Mr. Drut PS 57 Bronx Spanish Class, Nov 5, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12872)
  - Secretaries Committee, Edith Duffy, Oct 12, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13523)
  - IS 316 Brooklyn Para-Professional Bonnie Durden, May 10, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13278)
  - Jamaica High School Owen Engel, Jan 24, 1957 (Box 1, Item 3416)
  - PS 126 Early Childhood Miss Helen Ephros, Mrs. Marylin Barr, Raquel Zapata Para-Pro., Apr 8, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12491)
  - Retired Teachers - Congressman [ Leonard] Farbstein, Apr 24, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12537)
  - Afro-American Week Displays PS 25 [# 12392-4: Teacher Roberta Fass tells her students about labor leaders, A. Philip Randolph. Left to Right: Edgar Diaz, Darnell Norris, Neal McCord, Larry Gilliam, Roberta Fass, and Tyrone Temple.], Feb 13, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12392)
  - Joe Ferris Congressman #5 only 4 people on right, Apr 3, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8219)
  - District 1 George Fesko, Jan 15, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11593)
  - PS 497 Bronx Joan Fisher, Jan 13, 1969 (Box 6, Item 11590)